[
  {
    "question": "3 + 5 = ?",
    "options": ["6", "7", "8", "9"],
    "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
    "points": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "10 - 4 = ?",
    "options": ["5", "3", "7", "6"],
    "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
    "points": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "7 * 3 = ?",
    "options": ["20", "21", "22", "23"],
    "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
    "points": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "20 / 4 = ?",
    "options": ["5", "9", "6", "7"],
    "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
    "points": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "14 + 6 = ?",
    "options": ["18", "2", "19", "20"],
    "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
    "points": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "18 - 9 = ?",
    "options": ["7", "9", "10", "11"],
    "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
    "points": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "8 * 4 = ?",
    "options": ["30", "32", "34", "36"],
    "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
    "points": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "27 / 3 = ?",
    "options": ["8", "11", "10", "9"],
    "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
    "points": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "25 + 36 = ?",
    "options": ["61", "62", "63", "64"],
    "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
    "points": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "15 * 15 = ?",
    "options": ["210", "225", "240", "250"],
    "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
    "points": 3
  }
]
